Thomas Ankers

8 Southwood Close Kingswinford, DY6 8JL **07947693947 thomasjamesankers@gmail.com**

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced software engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. A perfectionist who is dedicated and has a willingness to excel. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Computer Science.

EXPERIENCE

Talkout, Birmingham — Senior Software Engineer

AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

Development of VR training courses. Managed shared libraries for internal and external teams. Developed and maintained a learning management system platform in VR.

Virtual Reality Simulation Systems, Telford—Programmer

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2020

XR development for public education, Fire service, Police service, public rail and manufacturing sectors.

VOiD Applications, Wolverhampton— *Programmer*

AUGUST 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Using Unity Engine to develop mobile applications.

EDUCATION

Birmingham City University, Birmingham — BSc Computer Science

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2018 1st Class Degree with Honours

Stourbridge College, Stourbridge— IT Extended Diploma

SEPTEMBER 2012 - MAY 2014

Triple Distinction

SKILLS

Agile Management

SCRUM

Solid OOP Principles

Production Management

UI/UX Design

Level Design

Game Flow

Client Liaison

Understanding of Platform Limitations

SOFTWARE

Unity 3D, Git, .NET Core, Xamarin, AWS, Azure, XCode, Android, Unreal Engine, MySQL

HARDWARE

Oculus Quest, Pico Neo/Geo, HTC Vive, Hololens, Android, iPhone, Windows Desktop

FRAMEWORKS

XR, Vuforia, MRToolkit, Steam VR, Pico SDK, Oculus Integration

LANGUAGES

C#, Java, Swift, C++, PHP, SQL, YML, & Others